(Sheldon:)Because I'd like to erase Ben Affleck
as Daredevil.
(Howard:)So would Ben Affleck.
(Howard:)The point is, in a situation like this,
you gotta pick sides.
(Howard:)You're either on team Leonard
or team Penny.
(Sheldon:)-Which one picks last?
-What?
(Sheldon:)Usually, I'm on the team
that picks last.
(Sheldon:)Unless there's a kid in a wheelchair.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I got you
your tangerine chicken.
(Leonard:)I hope you're hungry.
(Sheldon:)Well, of course I'm hungry.
(Sheldon:)And as I have no plans
to eat with any other team...
(Sheldon:)...I will consume my tangerine chicken
with the appropriate gusto.
(Sheldon:)Mm, mm, mm.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Just out of curiosity,
do we still have hot dogs?
(Leonard:)I don't know. Why?
(Sheldon:)Just making dinner conversation.
(Sheldon:)Go team Leonard.